Ok we are just about finished here.
I think that's a beautiful classic hair cut.
Classic and beautiful is what we are going for here.
A classic men's hair cut.
My name is Sylvia Russell and this is how you can get a clean classic men's hair cut.
Now first thing on my client Matt is that I like to keep it low.
Keep it nice and clean and neat.
Classic means very conservative, keeping it easy to maintain.
Nothing that needs a whole lot of work.
As I work my way up the side of the head, I'm going to leave it a little bit longer because I'm actually creating a fade.
Leaving it low on the bottom, higher on the top.
Once I'm done with my clippers, I'll go in with my shears making sure that I get all the leftover hair and that I make it even throughout.
Now this is something that you and a friend or your mom and dad can do at home.
But if you are not sure on how to get a good classic men's haircut, visit your local professional.
I'm sure they can help you choose the right cut that's for you.
Now Matt is just about done.
We've done the sides, we've done the middle and we've done the top and Matt likes his little spiky.
Always finish with a little hair spray.
And you've got a clean and classic men's hair cut.
My name is Sylvia Russell and this is how you can get a clean classic men's hair cut.